<resources>
    <string name="app_name">UniTour</string>
    <string name="facebook_app_id">1862027007408127</string>
    <string name="facebook_provider_id">facebook.com</string>

    <string name="loc_name_1">Kastari</string>
    <string name="loc_name_2">Tietotalo</string>
    <string name="loc_name_3">Datagarage</string>
    <string name="loc_name_4">Sodankylä Geophysical Observatory</string>
    <string name="loc_name_5">AISEC</string>
    <string name="loc_name_6">IT services</string>
    <string name="loc_name_7">Tellus</string>
    <string name="loc_name_8">FabLab</string>
    <string name="loc_name_9">Main Lobby</string>
    <string name="loc_name_10">Central Station</string>
    <string name="loc_name_11">Student Center</string>
    <string name="loc_name_12">Aava</string>
    <string name="loc_name_13">Zoological Museum</string>
    <string name="loc_name_14">Pegasus Library</string>
    <string name="loc_name_15">Balance</string>
    <string name="loc_name_16">Faculty of Education</string>

    <string name="loc_description_1">Located in the administration building, there is the 100-seat restaurant Kastari and the
        30-seat cabinet kastare. Daily food in the restaurant is delicious and soup of the day manufactured by the chef
        is available.\nKastari carries out the order of Cabinet lunches and other catering. The professional staff will
        tailor services and catering for different occasions.\nTogether with Saalasti hall and lobby in the main building
        in the University, Kastari forms a unique space with a 1430-seat holding company events, dinners, meetings, seminars,
        banquets and entertainment events needs.\nOpening time: Mon-Thu 8:00-17:30, Fri 8:00-14:30</string>
    <string name="loc_description_2">If you choose to study for example Information Processing Science, Electrical Engineering
        or Computer Science and Engineering, Tietotalo will be your “home” at the university. Take a look at the first day of
        new students of computer science and engineering at the university!\nhttp://www.oulu.fi/itee/node/40560</string>
    <string name="loc_description_3">Big size, lots of flavour. Nobody leaves our place hungry! Our home food-based lunch makes
        a big impression with its no-nonsense, delicious and plentiful selection. It includes familiar classics and delicious
        favourites from around the world. For more energy, have our protein-rich breakfasts and snacks. Make yourself at hom
        e in the rugged "man cave"!\nOpening time: Mon-Thu 9:00-15.00, Fri 9:00-14:30</string>
    <string name="loc_description_4">The Sodankylä Geophysical Observatory performs continuous measurements of the Earth\'s
        magnetic field, cosmic radio noise, seismic activities, and cosmic rays. Altogether SGO runs measurements in 19
        different locations from southern Finland to Svalbard.\nMore info in Finnish: http://www.oulu.fi/sgo/\n
        More info in English: http://www.oulu.fi/sgoenglish/
</string>
    <string name="loc_description_5">AIESEC is the world\'s largest non-profit student-run organization. It is an international
        non-governmental not-for-profit organization that provides young people with leadership development and cross-cultural
        global internship and volunteer exchange experiences across the globe, with a focus to empower young people so they
        can make a positive impact on society. The AIESEC network includes approximately 70,000 members in 127 countries and
        territories. It is the largest youth-run organization in the world</string>
    <string name="loc_description_6">IT Administration Services are responsible for the administration and operation of the
        University\'s data network, computer system maintenance, software and the promotion of information security. IT
        Services produce services for the research, teaching, studying, administration and for different interest groups.\n\n
        What they can provide:\n— university\'s user account and activation of a new account\n— password and how to change
        it\n— e-mail and activating of O365 service\n— workstations for student use on Linnanmaa kampus\n— wireless
        networks panOULU and eduroam\n— free software for students and software sale\n— helpdesk services of IT
        Administration</string>
    <string name="loc_description_7">Tellus Innovation Arena is a brand new, inspiring open space for learning, collaboration
        and entrepreneurship at the heart of University of Oulu\'s Linnanmaa campus and its multidisciplinary community.
        It was created for all you open-minded explorers from both inside and outside of the University to help you meet
        people, get in touch with some of the best experts in town and beyond, expand your networks, develop ideas, share
        your knowledge, present your projects and create valuable things together with others.\nMore info in English:
        http://www.oulu.fi/tellusarena/\nMore info in Finnish: http://www.oulu.fi/tellusarena-fi/ </string>
    <string name="loc_description_8">Fab Lab Oulu is a small digital manufacturing working area (fabrication laboratory)
        that complies with open innovation concept developed by MIT in the United States. In Fab Lab it is possible to design
        your own product or hardware from the scratch.\nMore info in English http://www.oulu.fi/fablab/ </string>
    <string name="loc_description_9">Bring various activities into your daily life. There are events happen in the university
        everyday and here is one of the place to witness them take place. Here you can meet International Mother Language
        Day, Career Day,Abipäivät, get to know new friends and buy your latest party tickets.</string>
    <string name="loc_description_10">The cities of the world on your plate: The bright colours and international flavours of
        the big city food courts bring friends together! At our grill stations you will find the best in street food:
        from tender strips of pulled pork to hot dogs and from stir fries to pizza slices. Fill your plate with tasty
        delights straight from South America or pop in for a visit to Asia. The Deli Salad Bar will serve you when you
        want to take it easy and light.\nOpening time: Mon-Thu 10.00-16.00, Fri 10.00-14.30.</string>
    <string name="loc_description_11">Student Center provides comprehensive services for students starting with registration
        to the university and going all the way to alumni services. The Student Center offers services to all students
        including exchange students and doctoral students, and also students who wish to take courses in the Open
        University.\nMore info about studies in English: http://www.oulu.fi/university/node/34985\nMore info about studies
        in Finnish: http://www.oulu.fi/yliopisto/opiskelijakeskus</string>
    <string name="loc_description_12">Experience the exotic North and harmonious Scandinavian interior design! We conjure up
        taste sensations where classic recipes combine with modern influences from both the East and West. Our menu has
        casual meat and fish dishes, colourful salads, the best seasonal soups and vegetable stews. Rye bread, oatmeal
        porridge and fresh buns makes a good start for the day.\nOpening time:Mon-Thu 7.45-18.30, Fri 8.30-18.00,
        Sat 9.00-15.00</string>
    <string name="loc_description_13">The museum forms an integral part of an international network of natural science
        museums functioning as a repository of knowledge and an expert body on biodiversity-related issues.\n
        More info in English http://www.oulu.fi/biodiversityunit/node/16772\n
        More info in Finnish http://www.oulu.fi/biodiversiteettiyksikko/node/1372</string>
    <string name="loc_description_14">Oulu University Library is a scientific library whose task is to provide library
        and    information services for the researchers, teachers and students of the University of Oulu.The Library is
        open to all public.\nMore info about studies in English: http://www.oulu.fi/library/\nMore info about studies in
        Finnish: http://www.oulu.fi/kirjasto/</string>
    <string name="loc_description_15">The aim is to understand that finding a balance with our families, friends, careers, school,
        sports and so much more can be a challenge. They are offering an alternative to sacrificing the way you feel after
        eating fast food with a fresh homemade approach ready within minutes.\nOpening time: mon-thu 8.30-14.30, lunch
        10.00 - 14.30; fri 8.30-14.00, lunch 10.00 - 14.00</string>
    <string name="loc_description_16">The Faculty of Education is a multidisciplinary expert organisation for training,
        research and development in the field of education and teaching.The Faculty provides high-quality education and
        research in a multidisciplinary and international academic environment. In addition to Bachelor\'s and Master\'s
        degrees, the Faculty offers a variety of postgraduate and continuing education opportunities. There are numerous
        research groups and projects which function in different cooperation and development projects in both the public
        and the private sector.There is also a teacher training school functioning under the auspices of the Faculty of
        Education.\nMore info in English http://www.oulu.fi/edu/admissions\nMore info in Finnish
        http://www.oulu.fi/ktk/opiskelijavalinta</string>

    <string name="noInternet">Your internet connection is turned off</string>

    <string name="infoActivity">UniTour application is created to help guests and visitors of the University of Oulu
        to get acquainted with the most significant locations of the campus. Sign up to play a QR quest or just explore
        the university map without any registration.\n\nCreated by Team A for the Software Factory Project course in 2017.
        \n\nhttp://unitour.000webhostapp.com/</string>

</resources>
